bdtask.com 2019-12-06

# Bdtask Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which bdtask collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.bdtask.com website ("Site").

### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

### How we use collected information bdtask may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

To run and operate our Site We may need your information display content on the Site correctly. To improve customer service Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently. To personalize user experience We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. To improve our Site We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services. To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them. To send periodic emails We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

### How we protect your information :

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

### Sharing your personal information : 

We will not share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.

### Electronic newsletters : 

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

### Changes to this privacy policy : 

bdtask has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms :

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

### Contacting us : 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.

This document was last updated on Dec 15, 2017
